hymoo.com 2009-12-03

# Hymoo Privacy Policy

On Hymoo, we pull out all the stops to keep the information you give us stay as safe as possible. We follow strict security procedures on how your personal information is stored and used, and who sees it, to help stop any unauthorized person getting hold of it. Hymoo follows the Data Protection Act 1998 and is registered on the public register of data controllers maintained by the Information Commissioner.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time. You should visit our Web site periodically to review any changes.

**Get in touch**  
You can get in touch by visiting the contact us section. 

For enquiries directly relating to Hymoo.com, you can contact us by clicking here.

**Personal details**  
We collect personal details, such as your email address, name, date of birth and other information only when you register with us for competitions, promotions or when you sign up to receive email newsletters from us.

When you register with us, we'll need to ask you for your:  
\- Username  
\- Email address  
\- Password  
\- Date of birth  

We will also automatically record your  
\- IP address - We collect your IP address to minimize fraud and to also analyze our web traffic trends.  
\- Internet Browser  
\- Operation System

If you want to tell us a bit more about yourself, we'd love to hear even more, like your:  
\- Postal Address and Postcode  
\- Mobile phone number  
\- Education  
\- Gender

We may wish to contact you from time to time with details of special offers, promotions, competitions, and information about our products and services. If you want all of this, please tick the box marked 'yes' when registering with us. We won't ever use your details for direct marketing without your consent. We may disclose your personal and account information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, as required by law, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Your personal and account information may also be disclosed in connection with a sale of some or all of our business or a merger with another company. Your personal and account information will never be disclosed to other third parties.

**Safe and sure**  
Our website has security installed to ensure that any personal data entered onto the site is protected against loss, misuse or alteration. However, due to the nature of the Internet, we can't guarantee the protection of your personal information and we can't be responsible for any outcomes resulting from a breach of security when the website is used. We're confident in our security, and it is always a top priority to ensure we do not get any problems.

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" to store and collect information regarding your usage of the website. Cookies are small files placed on your computer's hard drive, or in your browser memory, when you visit our website. They enable us to put in place personal settings and load your personal preferences.

**Update personal information**  
You can update your personal information at any time. Use your username and password to log in, and then you'll be able to update your information.

**Third Party:**  
Please keep in mind that Hymoo is a user-generated website. Therefore, we do not take responsibility if you share your information with any managers or any members here. Consider it as your own risk.
